Now, let's see how to rotate an array by Cape Position, rotate the element of an array clockwise by
one digit.
This is the question.
This is how you ask it in their interviews or in their exam.
So let's see how to resolve it in animation.
This is the array.
This is barely 10, 20, 30, 40 and 50.
We need to rotate the element of array clockwise by one digit, though, so think about this is the
array and we are rotating it to the right.
So the Element 50 would go and do that first.
This is how we rotate an element by cape position and get equal to one.
We are just making and rotating it by one digit to the right.
Now, let's see how in code, how to make this happens.
So in order to rotate the array right, we need to make a function called the rotate right.
It took into to meter array and array and and an OK.
And I and end them equal array at and minus one.
OK.
We have created a temporary integer that took the value of a rate at the last index.
And stored, it temporarily looked like.
So you guys.
10, 20, 30, 40 and 50 this hour array, we need to rotate it.
But first, I need to initialize a new variable called stamp.
I give at a rate and minus one, which is the last index of this array, the value to air.
So 50 is the same as temporary.
This is the variable, and we need to go through the loop through this this array and see how it works.
We start from I equal and minus one.
We start from the last and we go backwards through this loop.
Why?
Because we are rotating to the right.
OK, so we need to switch the element from the last to the first.
This one happens in searching array of equal array of I minus one.
OK.
And the switching this back.
And putting 50 at the first by getting the array of zero equal to 10.
So let me show you again.
We have removed 50 and stored it into temp and we are going through you through this loop.
This four loop array at Index eight equal array of Index I minus one.
So we are getting the previous previous value of elements, OK, and now we have done everything.
We have finished the loop, but there is an empty space.
So the empty space?
We get it from there.
Stamp by assigning array at index zero equal to 10.
OK.
This is that this is the algorithm of how to make and rotate that in order to test this.
You can make an array, rotate, array, the array and end and indicate that your eye and rotate the
array.
How many times you need to make that array and or how many times you need to rotate the array.
This is a generally rotating array, but we have applied this fork equal to one.
So we need to just rotate it by one digit.
OK, guys.
We have solved this exercise by by engineering, and we have created their rotating and array by cape
position.
But this, as example, is rotating that array by K. equal to one which had fast, which had the 50
from the last position.